Finding Aid for the American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California Records LSC.0900
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Archive, 1969
  - Civil liberties., 1969 (Box 190)
  - Communications, Media Committee (Box 191)
    900/N bx.7
  - National A.C.L.U. Docket of new cases. (Box 191)
  - Due process committee. (Box 191)
  - Equality committee. (Box 191)
  - Fair trial - Free Press. Policy -., Dec. 1966 (Box 191)
  - Free speech association committee., 1969 (Box 191)
  - Finance & membership - National. (Box 191)
  - Inside A.C.L.U. (Box 191)
  - Labor/business committee., 1969 (Box 191)
  - Legislative Advocate - Speiser. (Box 191)
  - National Board A.C.L.U. Minutes, 1969 (Box 192)
    900/N bx.8
  - National Board. Finances, budget, etc.., 1969 (Box 192)
  - National Board. Office memos. (Box 192)
  - National Board. Civil disorders. (Box 192)
  - National development Council. (Box 192)
  - National planning - 50th Anniversary. (Box 192)
  - News release. National A.C.L.U. (Box 192)
  - Nominative committee. (Box 192)
  - Privacy committee. (Box 192)
  - U.C.L.A. chapter. (Box 192)
  - Beverly Hills-Westwood chapter. Bulletin and mailings., 1965-1970 (Box 192)
  - Canyon chapter (Box 192)
    NOTE: Users interested in local chapters please note that the above 3 folders have been included in a national A.C.L.U. box.
  - Abortion., (1966, 1967) (Box 193)
  - Abortion materials - Current. (Box 193)
  - Abortion Sub-Committee (literature, etc.). (Box 193)
  - Academic Freedom Committee., 1970 (Box 193)
  - Anagnos, Carolyn - Correspondence. (Box 193)
  - Anagnos, Carolyn - Memos (interoffice). (Box 193)
  - Americans Building Constitutionally, 1968 (Box 194)
    900 N, box 9
  - A.C.L.U. Affairs (Garden Party, Bill of Rights Dinner, etc.). (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Board of Directors, National. Minutes. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Board of Directors, National. Executive Committee. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. National docket. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. National Development CouncilSteering Committee,., 1970 (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. National Office & finances. Budget. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Distribution list (mailing labels). (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Small claims court. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Miscellaneous documents, notices, etc.,., 1969 (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. News releases, national. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Office memos - to Board of Directors, National. (Box 194)
  - A.C.L.U. Southern California. Press releases. (Box 194)
  - Arrest & trial. (Box 194)
  - Arts Division. Play Contest., 1968 (Box 194)
  - Roger Baldwin Foundation. (Box 195)
  - Berkeley,., May, 1969 (Box 195)
  - Bienniel Conference. Papers and resolutions,., 1968 (Box 195)
  - Bienniel Conference -., 1970 (Box 195)
  - Bill of Rights. (Box 195)
  - Bill of Rights Banquet,., 1968 (Box 195)
  - Bill of Rights Dinner,., 1969 (Box 195)
  - Bill of Rights Dinner, Working materials., 1969. (Box 195)
  - Bill of Rights. Program, 50th Anniversary (Box 196)
    900C.box4
  - Board of Directors, So. Cal., correspondence. (Box 196)
  - Board of Directors, So. Cal., minutes, (2 folders) (Box 196)
  - Board of Directors, So. Cal., notices. (Box 196)
  - Budgets. A.C.L.U. of So. Cal. for., 1970 (Box 196)
  - Chicago Conspiracy 7. (Box 196)
  - Church/State Committee,., 1970 (Box 196)
  - Civil Liberties. (Box 196)
  - Civil Rights Act - Title VI., 1964. (Box 196)
  - Civil rights, speeches, etc. (Box 196)
  - Communications Media Committee. (Box 196)
  - Conscientious objectors & conscription - A.C.L.U. working papers. (Box 196)
  - Constitutional Rights Foundation. (Box 196)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous to A.C.L.U. (Box 196)
  - Due process Committee,., 1970 (Box 197)
  - Editorials TV and radio, etc.,., 1969 (Box 197)
  - Education - Board of Education, L.A. City. (Box 197)
  - El Camino Real High School. (Box 197)
  - Essay contest. Bill of Rights. (Box 197)
  - Education - equal education. (Box 197)
  - Equality Committee. Special -., 1968 (Box 197)
  - Executive Committee. (Box 197)
  - Executive directions - memos, etc. (Box 197)
  - Free Speech Association Committee. (Box 197)
  - Hopkins, Prynce. (Box 197)
  - Housing,., 1968 (Box 198)
  - Housing, Proposition 14. (Box 198)
  - Housing. Operation Open City. (Box 198)
  - Inside A.C.L.U. Publication. (Box 198)
  - Labor Business Committee. (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Academic freedom. (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Church and State. (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Due process & equal protection, (2 folders) (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Lawyers Division Executive Committee. Minutes,., 1969 (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Lawyers Division Executive Committee. Notices, memos, minutes, etc.,., 1970 (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. First ammendment. (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Juvenile rights. (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Military justice. (Box 198)
  - Lawyers Division. Miscellaneous correspondence. (Box 199)
  - Lawyers Division. Rights of privacy. (Box 199)
  - Lawyers Division. Rights of public employees. (Box 199)
  - Legislative Action. Northern California. (Box 199)
  - Legislative Advocate. Registration. (Box 199)
  - Legislative Advocate. Washington, D.C. (Box 199)
  - Levering oath. Kenney decision. (Box 199)
  - Levy case. (Box 199)
  - Los Angeles Neighborhood Legal Services Society, Inc. (Box 199)
  - Loyalty oaths. Medicare. Hawaii - Arizona opinion. (Box 199)
  - Mace. (Box 199)
  - Manual Arts discipline transfers,., 1969 (Box 199)
  - Mental Health. Assembly Sub-Committee. (Box 199)
  - Opportunity transfer case. Jefferson High, Roy Warren case. (Box 200)
  - Opus (Eason Monroe, Alan Reilman). (Box 200)
  - Personnel Management Committee. (Box 200)
  - Police-community relations. (Box 200)
  - Police complaint procedure. (Box 200)
  - Police. East Los Angeles, Los Angeles, etc. (Box 200)
  - Police Malpractice Center - Report data (raw)., 1968 (Box 200)
  - Parks and Recreation hearings - police photographing. (Box 200)
  - Police photographing. (Box 200)
  - Police policies, Los Angeles Police Department. (Box 200)
  - Police records - expunging procedures. (Box 200)
  - Public relations (Ed Cray, news releases, etc.). (Box 200)
  - Race Relations Act, England,., 1968 (Box 200)
  - Recall Reagan Committee, Inc. (2 folders)., (1968) (Box 200)
  - Report of counsel,., 1969 (Box 200)
  - Riots. Anti-riot bills -., 1966 (Box 200)
  - Riots. Forms (A.C.L.U. forms for arrestees). (Box 200)
  - San Fernando Valley State College problem,., 1969 (Box 200)
  - San Fernando Valley State College. Suit to readmit demonstrating students. (Box 200)
  - San Fernando Valley State College. Newspaper clippings (Box 200)
    - Daily Sundial., 1-7-69 to 1-10-69 (Box 200)
    - Out Cry. (Box 200)
    - Open Campus. (Box 200)
    - Black Star. (Box 200)
    - Valley News & Green Sheet (West Valley ed.)., 1-8-69 to 1-14-69 (Box 200)
    - Campus memos. (Box 200)
    - Valley Times., 1-6 to 1-17 (Box 200)
    - L. A. Herald Examiner., 1-7 to 1-16 (Box 200)
    - L.A. Times (home delivery in West Valley)., 1-8 to 1-17-69 (Box 200)
  - San Fernando Valley State. incidents, etc., Nov. 4, Jan. 8 (Box 200)
  - San Fernando Valley State College. - Disturbance clippings, notes. (Box 201)
  - - College Information Bulletin, memos, flyers. (Box 201)
  - Social workers. (Box 201)
  - Dr. Spock. Indictments. (Box 201)
  - Vietnam - and civil liberties. (Box 201)
  - Welfare Committee, Health care., 1969. (Box 201)
  - Williams, M. J. Merchant Marine & Communist affidavit. (Box 201)
  - Women's division. (Box 201)
  - Local Chapters (Box 202)
    900 F. box 4
    - Alabama. (Box 202)
    - Alaska. (Box 202)
    - Arizona. (Box 202)
    - California (Box 202)
      - - Claremont-Pomona Chapter (Hall case). (Box 202)
      - - San Diego A.C.L.U. activity Legal panel. (Box 202)
      - - San Francisco. Northern California. (Box 202)
    - Colorado. (Box 202)
    - Connecticut. (Box 202)
    - District of Columbia. (Box 202)
    - Florida. (Box 202)
    - Georgia (& Southern Regional Office). (Box 202)
    - Hawaii. (Box 202)
    - Illinois. (Box 202)
    - Indiana & Iowa. (Box 202)
    - Japan Civil Liberties Union (Box 203)
      900 F. box 5
    - Kansas. (Box 203)
    - Louisiana. (Box 203)
    - Maryland/Maine. (Box 203)
    - Mass chusets. (Box 203)
    - Michigan. (Box 203)
    - Minnesota. (Box 203)
    - New Hampshire. (Box 203)
    - New Jersey. (Box 203)
    - New Mexico. (Box 203)
    - New York. (Box 203)
    - North Carolina. (Box 203)
    - Ohio. (Box 203)
    - Oklahoma. (Box 203)
    - Oregon. (Box 203)
    - Pennsylvania. (Box 203)
    - Texas. (Box 203)
    - Washington. (Box 203)
    - Wisconsin. (Box 203)
  - Closed cases. Venice. Police Malpractice Center. Individual folders on cases handled by the A.C.L.U. arranged alphabeticaly. (Box 204)
  - Closed cases. East Los Angeles. Police Malpractice Center.
    - A - Cel. (Box 205)
    - Cer - E. (Box 206)
    - Fab - Her. (Box 207)
    - Hir - Mar. (Box 208)
    - Mast - Ram. (Box 209)
    - Rec - Sims. (Box 210)
    - Smith - Z. (Box 211)
- Archive, 1970-71
  The following records were deposited October, 1973. As in previous deposits, some of the material covers earlier dates.
  - Academic Freedom Committee -., 1971 (Box 212)
  - ACLU Foundation (see also Roger Baldwin Foundation). (Box 212)
  - American Library Association -, 1970 (Box 212)
    Scope and Contents note
    (Newsletter on Intellectual Freedom)
  - Biennial conferences, (Resolutions)., 1968-1970 (Box 212)
  - Black Panthers, (Dec. raids, etc.)., 1969-1970 (Box 212)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence. (Box 212)
  - Board of Directors, Minutes -., 1971 (Box 212)
  - Board of Directors, Notices -., 1971 (Box 212)
  - Cases: (Box 212)
    - Beard cases - Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen. (Box 212)
    - Long Hair cases - Palletreau v. Bd. of Ed. N.J. (Box 212)
    - People v. Atkins & Davis - Yorty anti riot act. (Box 212)
    - School desegregation cases - San Diego and Bakersfield. (Box 212)
    - Century City - Documents II. (Box 212)
    - Church, - State Committee -., 1971 (Box 212)
    - Correspondence - (Caroline Anagnos)., 1971 (Box 212)
    - Davis, Angela. (Box 212)
    - Due Process Committee -., 1971 (Box 212)
    - Elysian Park - Easter -., 1971 (Box 212)
  - Equality Committee. (Box 213)
  - Executive Committee. (Box 213)
  - Executive Director. (Box 213)
  - Executive Director (Archives). (Box 213)
  - Fields, Danny. (Box 213)
  - Free Press - Narcotics Agents case. (Box 213)
  - Free Press and Media Committee. (Box 213)
  - Free Speech/Association Committee. (Box 213)
  - Free Speech/Association Committee -., 1971 (Box 213)
  - Free Speech/Association, Surveillance -., 1969 (Box 213)
  - Hoover Project. (Box 213)
  - Lawyers Division Executive Committee - Minutes -., 1970, 1971 (Box 213)
  - Legal Committee - Docket - San Diego. (Box 213)
  - Legal Panel - Eastern Region. (Box 213)
  - Loyalty oaths. (Box 213)
  - Loyalty oaths - Dilworth Act. (Box 213)
  - Marijuana - National Board. (Box 213)
  - Medical Services Committee. (Box 214)
  - Membership income. (Box 214)
  - Mental Health Services Committee. (Box 214)
  - National Board - Executive Committee -., 1971 (Box 214)
  - National Board Minutes -., 1971 (Box 214)
  - National Legal Docket - Roger Baldwin Foundation -., 1968 (Box 214)
  - National Mailings. (Box 214)
  - National Office news releases. (Box 214)
  - Neier and/or Board of Directors - To Affiliates -., 1971 (Box 214)
  - Nominating Committee (National). (Box 214)
  - Open Forum -., 1971 (Box 214)
  - Orders for literature, etc. (Box 214)
  - Pasadena Police Practices Complaint Center. (Box 214)
  - Pitchess, Sheriff Peter J. (Box 214)
  - Prison reform. (Box 214)
  - Privacy Committee -., 1971 (Box 214)
  - Program -., 1971 (Box 214)
  - Public Relations - New releases, etc. (Box 214)
  - Publications and Materials - (General). (Box 214)
  - Publications and Materials (by individual chapters) (Box 214)
    - Arizona. (Box 214)
    - California (Northern). (Box 214)
    - California (Southern, including local chapters). (Box 214)
    - Colorado. (Box 214)
    - Connecticut. (Box 214)
    - Florida. (Box 214)
    - Illinois. (Box 215)
    - Indiana. (Box 215)
    - Iowa. (Box 215)
    - Japan. (Box 215)
    - Kentucky. (Box 215)
    - Massachusetts. (Box 215)
    - Michigan. (Box 215)
    - Minnesota. (Box 215)
    - Mississippi. (Box 215)
    - New Hampshire. (Box 215)
    - New Mexico. (Box 215)
    - New York. (Box 215)
    - North Carolina. (Box 215)
    - Ohio. (Box 215)
    - Oregon. (Box 215)
    - Pennsylvania. (Box 215)
    - Southern Regional Office and Council. (Box 215)
    - Tennessee. (Box 215)
    - Texas. (Box 215)
    - Vermont. (Box 216)
    - Virginia. (Box 216)
    - Washington. (Box 216)
    - Wisconsin. (Box 216)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 216)
  - Religious celebrations in schools -., 1971 (Box 216)
  - Riot data. (Box 216)
  - Roger Baldwin Foundation - Budget, etc. -., 1970 (Box 216)
  - Rose Bowl - Half-time program -., 1971 (Box 216)
  - Santa Barbara Environmental Rights Committee. (Box 216)
  - Santa Barbara oil slick cases. (Box 216)
  - School Integration and Decentralization Committee. (Box 216)
  - Social Welfare - Proposed Policy -., 1967 (Box 216)
  - Staff - Job descriptions, functions, departments. (Box 216)
  - Student Rights Center. (Box 216)
  - Student Rights - Problems. (Box 216)
  - Sunday in the Park. (Box 216)
  - Van Peebles, Melvin. (Box 216)
  - Venice Welfare Complaint Office - History. (Box 216)
- Archive, 1972-73
  The following records were deposited April, 1974. As in previous enteries, some of the material covers earlier dates.
  - Academic Freedom Committee -., 1971-72. (Box 217)
  - Bakersfield Chapter -., 1970-71. (Box 217)
  - Biennial Conference -., 1972. (Box 217)
  - Board of Directors Minutes -., 1971-72. (Box 217)
  - CCCO - Newsletter on Military Law and Counseling -., 1970-71. (Box 217)
  - California Rural Legal Assistance -., 1969. (Box 217)
  - Calls for Assistance LOGS -., 1971. (Box 217)
  - Capital Punishment - Execution Data. (Box 217)
  - Carver Jr. High School -., March,1969. (Box 217)
  - Chapter - Affiliate Relations (Special Committee) -., 1970. (Box 217)
  - Church - State Committee Minutes -., 1971-72. (Box 217)
  - Civil Liberties -., 1971-73. (Box 217)
  - Communications Media Committee -., 1972. (Box 218)
  - Communications Media Committee -., 1971. (Box 218)
  - Constitution Committee. (Box 218)
  - Correspondence - Board of Directors. (Box 218)
  - Correspondence - Calif. -., 1972. (Box 218)
  - Docket - National. (Box 218)
  - Due Process Committee. (Box 218)
  - Equality Committee -., 1972. (Box 218)
  - Executive Committee -., 1972. (Box 218)
  - Executive Direction. (Box 218)
  - Free Speech/Association Committee. (Box 219)
  - Lawyers Division Executive Committee Minutes -., 1972. (Box 219)
  - Mental Commitment Memorandum -., 1971. (Box 219)
  - Military and Bill of Rights - Special Committee -., 1971. (Box 219)
  - Minutes - Board of Directors -., 1972. (Box 219)
  - Minutes - Executive Committee -., 1972. (Box 219)
  - National Development Council - Ninth Conference,., June 6, 1972. (Box 219)
  - National Office Memos to Affiliates and Committees. (Box 219)
  - National Office News Releases. (Box 219)
  - National Office Publications. (Box 219)
  - Police-Community Relations. (Box 219)
  - Prisoners' Rights - National Conference -., 1971. (Box 219)
  - Privacy Committee -., 1972. (Box 219)
  - Report of Counsel -., 1972. (Box 219)
  - Selective Service - C.O. - etc. (Box 219)
  - Student Vote. (Box 219)
  - Student Vote (National) - Residency - etc. (Box 219)
  - Miscellaneous Local Chapters. (Collected by UCLA Dept. of Spec. Coll.). (Box 219)
- Archive, 1974-1976
  The following records were deposited September, 1977. As in previous entries, some of the material covers earlier dates.
  - Abortion - Belous case, ACLU briefs. (Box 220)
  - Abortion - Supreme Court decision, Jan.., 1973. (Box 220)
  - Academic freedom,., 1973. (Box 220)
  - Activity reports -., 1973. (Box 220)
  - Adams & Sullivan - court case. (Box 220)
  - Adoption policy. (Box 220)
  - Airport Search Committee. (Box 220)
  - Alcoholism - Court decision. (Box 220)
  - Allen, Steve - letter to Frank Sinatra. (Box 220)
  - Allen - Trumbo correspondence. (Box 220)
  - ACLU - Attacks and answers. (Box 220)
  - ACLU - Constitution (Nate)., 1974. (Box 220)
  - ACLU Foundation Pamphlet proposal. (Box 220)
  - ACLU responses to Communist charges by Right Wing, etc. (Box 220)
  - American Jewish Congress - case decisions. (Box 220)
  - American Jewish Congress - cases pending. (Box 221)
  - American Jewish Congress correspondence. (Box 221)
  - Applicants - Executive Director ACLU. (Box 221)
  - Arrest records. (Box 221)
  - Attorney Genreal - California programs. (Box 221)
  - Attorney General's list - Executive Order recinded,., 1973. (Box 221)
  - Banking - Secrecy in Banking Act. (Box 221)
  - Bartoloni, Mark - court case. (Box 221)
  - Beaven vs. Wallace. (Box 221)
  - Bienniel Conference,., 1972. (Box 221)
  - Bienniel Conference,., 1972. (Box 222)
  - Bienniel Conference,., 1974. (Box 222)
  - Board of Corrections - Standards for Detention Facilities. (Box 222)
  - Board of Directors & Nominees - Biographies,., 1971-1974. (Box 222)
  - Board Minutes,., 1972-1973. (Box 222)
  - Board of Directors and Board Packet, Minutes of,., 1974. (Box 222)
  - Burns, Roosevelt. Police homocide,., 1971. (Box 222)
  - Bussing campaign. (Box 222)
  - By-Laws - ACLU of Southern California. (Box 222)
  - Cable TV. (Box 222)
  - Church - State Christmas Program,., 1971. (Box 222)
  - Children's rights. (Box 222)
  - Civil Liberties -., 1971-1972. (Box 223)
  - Civil Liberties -., 1973. (Box 223)
  - Civil Liberties -., 1974 (Box 223)
  - Civil Liberties - Acquisitions Meiklejohn Library. (Box 223)
  - Clark, Gregory - Inquest. (Box 223)
  - Constitution - ACLU & By-Laws. (Box 223)
  - Corporal punishment - Data on public schools. (Box 223)
  - Corporal punishment National Report. (Box 223)
  - Correspondence A-F., 1974 - (Box 223)
  - Correspondence G-K., 1974 - (Box 224)
  - Correspondence L-O., 1974 - (Box 224)
  - Correspondence P-Z., 1974 - (Box 224)
  - Counsel, Report of.., 1976. (Box 224)
  - Crawford Decision. (Box 224)
  - Criminal Justice Lobby. (Box 224)
  - Criminal Procedure Committee Reports - Alan Sieroty. (Box 224)
  - Davis, Police Chief. (Box 225)
  - Draft - Repeal of. (Box 225)
  - Drugs - in High Schools, survey., 1971 (Box 225)
  - Earthquake - SBA Suit. (Box 225)
  - Editorials - Press, Radio, TV, & Responses. (Box 225)
  - Education & Civil Liberties. (Box 225)
  - Election regulations. (Box 225)
  - Ellsberg. (Box 225)
  - Equality Committee. (Box 225)
  - Executive Committee,., 1972-1974. (Box 225)
  - Executive Director (RR). (Box 225)
  - Executive Privilege. (Box 225)
  - Fair trial; Free press. (Box 225)
  - Farm Workers Committee. (Box 225)
  - Flag case - A test for Old Glory. (Box 225)
  - Fluoridation. (Box 225)
  - Freedom of Information Act. (Box 225)
  - Frontera. (Box 225)
  - Gambling laws - Hawaii. (Box 225)
  - Greenleaf Classics. (Box 225)
  - Habeas Corpus procedures. (Box 225)
  - Hatch, Dan - Security clearance. (Box 225)
  - Health Law Program - National. (Box 225)
  - Health Services Committee. (Box 225)
  - HISC - Black Panther Party Report. (Box 225)
  - Homosexuals Docket. (Box 225)
  - Homosexuals - Problems. (Box 225)
  - Immunity - Contempt - Grand Juries. (Box 226)
  - Impeachment. (Box 226)
  - Impeachment Campaign - National Campaign. (Box 226)
  - Impeachment - Conviction. (Box 226)
  - Impeachment proposal, etc. (Box 226)
  - Impounds - Savings & Loans complaints. (Box 226)
  - Inquest - Coroner - Ackerman. (Box 226)
  - Inquest study -., 1969. (Box 226)
  - Insurance, Unemployment, & Disability. (Box 226)
  - Internal Security Act - Detention Camps,., 1950. (Box 226)
  - Internal Security Sub-Committee (Thomas Report). (Box 226)
  - Jacoby & Meyers - court case. (Box 227)
  - Juvenile Justice - Assmebly Committee on Criminal Justice,., 1975. (Box 227)
  - Juvenile Rights Project - National. (Box 227)
  - Juveniles - Rights of. (Box 227)
  - Kenny - Pact Recall attempts. (Box 227)
  - Kleindeist. (Box 227)
  - Krishna Cult. (Box 227)
  - Kunstler - Wall Street Journal,., 11/28/69. (Box 227)
  - KVST - VISTAS. (Box 227)
  - Lancaster Police Brutality Incident -., April 1974. (Box 227)
  - Legislative Advocate - Testimony. (Box 227)
  - Legislative Advocate & others - Testimony to Congress,., 1971. (Box 227)
  - Legislative Advocate Memos. (Box 227)
  - Legislative Questionaire Responses -., January 1975. (Box 228)
  - Legislative Advocate Reports from Cole Blease. (Box 228)
  - Lewis vs. United States of America. (Box 228)
  - Libel - ACLU's position,., 1965. (Box 228)
  - Litigation Procedures & Practices - ACLU (Jurisdictors). (Box 228)
  - Long Hair Problems - Peckham and Wyzanski decisions. (Box 228)
  - Loyalty - Subversive Activites. (Box 228)
  - Loyalty Oaths - Presidential Executive Order,., 1971. (Box 228)
  - McCone Commission [Watts] & ACLU statements. (Box 228)
  - Mail Surveillance. (Box 228)
  - Marijuana. (Box 229)
  - Marijuana Petition. (Box 229)
  - Marijuana Policy - Soc. (Box 229)
  - Marijuana - Repeal Proposition. (Box 229)
  - Marijuana SB 95 - Moscone Bill,., 1974. (Box 229)
  - May Day Arrest Inquiry. (Box 229)
  - Medical Ethics - Civil Liberties. (Box 229)
  - Mental Illness - Reports. (Box 229)
  - Metzger, Dena - court case. (Box 229)
  - Mexican American population in California. (Box 229)
  - Mexican jails. (Box 229)
  - Monroe vs. Trustees of State College. California Supreme Court Decision. (Box 229)
  - Monroe, Eason - Tribute by La Ree Caughey. (Box 229)
  - Montag, Gustave - Chicano Moratorium,., 1/31/71. (Box 229)
  - Morgan, Charles (New Yorker). (Box 229)
  - NEA - Teacher's Bill of Rights. (Box 229)
  - Nudity. (Box 229)
  - Nursery School Fight. (Box 229)
  - Obscenity Initiative - Proposition., 18, 1972. (Box 229)
  - Ombudsman - ACLU News. (Box 229)
  - Open Forum:., 1973-1974. (Box 229)
  - Open Forum:., 1975-1976. (Box 229)
  - Orange County Legal Commission. (Box 230)
  - Organized Crime Control Act analysis -., 1970. (Box 230)
  - Paul Robeson Players. (Box 230)
  - Pearse, Danielle (Ins. problem). (Box 230)
  - Permits - Demonstrations, Rallys, etc. (Box 230)
  - Police Brutality - Watts,., 1968. (Box 230)
  - Police (Changing the) - The Impossible Dream. (Box 230)
  - Police Infiltration of Political Organizations. (Box 230)
  - Police - LAPD - Sheriff, etc. (Box 230)
  - Police Sweeps - schools. (Box 230)
  - Policy Revision #526. (Box 230)
  - Polygraph Tests - Shakey's Pizza Parlors. (Box 230)
  - Poverty -STMS. (Box 230)
  - Preventive Detention. (Box 230)
  - Prison conditions - Union Bill of Rights. (Box 230)
  - Prison Project - National. (Box 230)
  - Prisoners - Detention camp. (Box 230)
  - Prisoners' Rights Project. (Box 230)
  - Privacy. (Box 230)
  - Privacy Bill - SB852: ACLU/Moscone. (Box 230)
  - Privacy Committe (suicide paper). (Box 230)
  - Privacy - LAPD - Dossiers. (Box 230)
  - Privacy Paper. (Box 230)
  - Privacy - problems - DMV, Credit Bureau, etc. (Box 230)
  - Privacy - Student Records. (Box 230)
  - Proposition 9. (Box 231)
  - Prostitution. (Box 231)
  - Psychological Testing for Jobs. (Box 231)
  - Public Employees - Jobs refused due to arrest records. (Box 231)
  - Public Guardian. (Box 231)
  - Public Relations., 1974-1976. (Box 231)
  - Public Relations News Releases,., 1972-1973. (Box 231)
  - Publications Agreements. (Box 231)
  - Publications - National ACLU. (Box 231)
  - Questionnaire Forms. (Box 231)
  - Questionnaire - Westons Suggested Agency Questionnaire. (Box 231)
  - Racial & Ethic Survey - LA City Schools,., 1970. (Box 231)
  - Radio Spots - Scripts., (July 4) (Box 231)
  - Rape. (Box 231)